Guide to the Stanford University, Women's Physical Education Department, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1984-132
  - Class: Tennis, advanced, 1944 Fall (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Class: Tennis, intermediate, 1944 Fall (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Class: Tennis, doubles, 1945 Summer (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Class: Tennis, intermediate, 1945 Winter (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Class: Tennis, 1945 Fall (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Class: Tennis, 1945 Fall (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Class: Tennis, advanced, 1945 Winter (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Class: Tennis, 1946 Winter (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Class: Tennis, 1946 Winter (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Class: Tennis, 1946 Spring (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Class: Tennis, 1946 Fall (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Class: Tennis, 1946 Fall (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Class: Tennis, 1947 Winter (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Class: Tennis, 1947 Winter (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Class: Tennis, 1947 Fall (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Class: Tennis, 1947 Fall (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Class: Tennis, 1948 Spring (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Class: Tennis, 1948 Spring (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Class: Tennis, 1948 Fall (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Class: Tennis, 1950 Fall (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Class: Tennis: teaching notes, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Class: Tennis: course materials, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Class: Tennis, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Class: Tennis: final, 1958 Spring (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Class: Tennis: final, 1958 Spring (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Class: Tennis: course materials, 1958 Spring (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Class: Tennis, 1958 Spring (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Class: Tennis: teaching notes and course materials, 1965 Fall (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Class: Tennis: course materials, 1965 Fall (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Class: Tennis, 1965 Fall (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1960 Winter (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1960 Winter (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1960 Winter (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1960 Winter (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1960 Winter (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1961 Winter (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1961 Winter (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1961 Winter (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1961 Winter (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1961 Winter (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis: correspondence, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1963 Winter (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1963 Winter (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1963 Spring (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1963 Spring (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1965 Winter (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1965 Winter (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1966 Winter (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1966 Winter (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1966 Winter (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1967 Winter (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Class: Tournament Tennis, 1967 Winter (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: correspondence, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: teaching notes, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials and teaching notes, 1945-1953 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: correspondence, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: student work, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: teaching notes, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: teaching notes, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: teaching notes, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: correspondence, 1951 Spring (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1951 Spring (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: evaluations, 1951 Spring (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: student work, 1951 Spring (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: correspondence and teaching materials, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: correspondence, teaching notes, student work, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: correspondence and teaching notes, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: student work, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: correspondence, teaching notes, and student work, 1957 Spring (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1957 Spring (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1957 Spring (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: correspondence and teaching notes, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: student work, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation: course materials, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Class: Trends and Practices in Recreation, 1961 Spring (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Golf: records, 1931-1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Golf: records, 1949-1954 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Golf: records, 1955-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Golf: records, 1955-1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Golf: records, 1965-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Golf: records, 1965-1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Golf: records, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Golf: records, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Tennis: club, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Tennis: club, 1933-1937 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Tennis: club, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tennis: club, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tennis: club, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Tennis: club, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Tennis: club, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Tennis: club, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Tennis: club, junior, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Tennis: club, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Tennis: club, 1947 Spring (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Tennis: club, 1947 Fall (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Tennis: club, 1948 Spring (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Tennis: inter-club, Undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Tennis: inter-club, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Tennis: Northern California Tennis Association, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Tennis: Northern California Tennis Association: yearbooks, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tennis: Officials, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: minutes of organization meeting, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: preliminary material, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: correspondence, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: sanction, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: publicity, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: entries, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: draw and last meeting, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: court assignments, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: officials, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: tournament correspondence, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: policies, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: draw sheets, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Athletic Association of Western Universities: evaluation, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Ojai, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Northern California Tennis Association, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Tennis Tournaments: Northern California Tennis Association, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Tennis Tournaments: USLTA Women's National Collegiate, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Tennis Tournaments: USLTA Women's National Collegiate, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Tennis Tournaments: USLTA Women's National Collegiate, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, blank questionnaires, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Mills College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Mills College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Mills College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Mills College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Mills College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Mills College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Mills College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Stanford University, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Stanford University, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from Stanford University, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from University of New Mexico, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from University of New Mexico, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from University of New Mexico, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from University of New Mexico, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from University of Wyoming, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from University of Wyoming, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from University of Wyoming, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, responses from University of Wyoming, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, various papers, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, various papers, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Survey: Western Society of Physical Education for College Women, various papers, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Survey: Far West Ski Association blank questionnaires, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Survey: Far West Ski Association responses, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Survey: Far West Ski Association correspondence, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Finnish National Game, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Publications: House and Garden, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Pictures: Margaret C. Barr, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Stanford Folk dancers, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Stanford Folk dancers, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Stanford Folk dancers, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Stanford Folk dancers, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Stanford Folk dancers, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Stanford Folk dancers, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Stanford Folk dancers, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - American Association for Health, Physical Education and Recreation: recruitment principles, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - California Association for Health, Physical Education and Recreation: recreational platform, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Intercollegiates, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Intercollegiates, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - International Education, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy, H. W.: Speech on legal issues, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Northern California Women's Intercollegiate Council, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Northern California Women's Intercollegiate Council, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Phi Delta Pi, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Sadlo, Lola Marie: excerpt from dissertation on recreational leadership, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Publications: Alabama Association for Health, Physical Education and Recreation, Handbook, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Publications: Baseball Rules, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Publications: California North, Girls and Women's Sports, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Publications: Georg, Hans, Skiing Simplified, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Publications: Softball rules, 1947, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Publications: Souvenir annual for tennis, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Publications: Stanford Football Facts, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Publications: Stanford Women's Physical Education Newsletter, 1965, 1966, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Publications: Stanford Women's Recreation Association, Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Publications: University of Arizona, Intramural Sports, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1985-034
  [Stanford Hoedowners joined with the Stanford Village Folk Dancers in May 1953 to become the Stanford Folk Dancers.]
  - Stanford Hoedowners records, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Hoedowners records, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hoedowners records, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Hoedowners records, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Hoedowners Photos (prints), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Hoedowners records, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Hoedowners Photos (prints), 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Hoedowners records, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Hoedowners records, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Hoedowners Photos (prints), 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers records, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers records, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers records, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers Photos (prints), 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers records, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers records, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers Photos (negatives and prints), 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers records, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers Photos (negatives and prints), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers Photos (negatives and prints), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers records, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers Photos (prints), 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers Photos (prints), 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Folk Dance Publications, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - History of Folk Dances, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Mad Night, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Miriam Lidster, information on, 1976, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous events – Photos, Programs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Notes to accompany film of Jugoslav Folk Dances, Dennis C. Boxell, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Juan Valenzuela, clippings about, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Recorded material, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Spring Migration, programs and clipping, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Annual Folk Dance Festival, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers – Constitution and History, ca., 1950-1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers – Misc. material, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers Photos (negatives and proofs), Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Folk Dancers various performances, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Various sheet music and instructions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Venue requests of Stanford Folk Dancers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Women's Recreation Association / Women's Athletic Association., Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Annual Newsletter, Accession ARCH-2008-100
  - Bound volume of Physical Education for Women Annual Newsletter, 1957-1963 (Box 1)